던전 입구는 이끼로 덮여 있다
*던전 : 지하 감옥
"The entrance to the dungeon
is a moss covered door.
힘겹게 문을 열자
"You manage to open it
only to find yourself
이끼로 덮인 괴물과
대면하게 되었다
"face-to-face with a hideous,
foul-smelling,
moss-covered ogre."
어떻게 할래?
What do you do?
'엄마, 저녁 메뉴 뭐야?'
라고 물어볼래
I say, "Hey, Ma,
what's for dinner?"
Seventeen.
괴물은 네 농담에 낄낄대며
지나가도록 허락한다
The ogre is amused by your joke
and allows you to pass.
참, 나까지 웃겼어
By the by, I liked it, too.
하워드, 결혼 준비는 잘 되가?
How go the wedding plans,
Howard?
어젯밤 5시간 동안
메이시에서 선물 골랐어
Great.
We spent five hours last night
at Macy's registering for gifts.
도기 아스파라거스 접시를
받아볼 수 있을 거야
Looks like I'm finally going
to have
that darling little earthenware
asparagus dish
I've always wanted.
거봐, 난 여친이 9천마일
떨어져 있어서 편하잖아
See, this is the good thing
about having a girlfriend
9,000 miles away.
시간도 내 마음대로 보내고
I can spend my nights
doing whatever I want.
우리랑 찌질한 게임이나 하고
You mean like playing nerd games
with us
샤워는 수상하게
오래 걸리던데
and then taking
a suspiciously long shower?
그랬던가
Maybe.
던전에 들어간다
We enter the dungeon.
드래곤이 보인다
You see a dragon.
'던전 앤 드래곤'이라서
Really? So we're playing
Dungeons & Dragons
던전에 들어가니
드래곤이 보이는 거야?
and we walk into a dungeon
and see a dragon?
너무 뻔하지 않아?
Isn't that a little
on the nose?
'뱀과 사다리'에서는
When you play Chutes and
Ladders, do you complain
뱀이랑 사다리가
많은 게 당연하잖아
about all the chutes
and all the ladders?
파이 다 먹을 거야?
Are you gonna eat
that whole pie?
아마도, 왜?
Maybe. Why not?
누구한테 보여줄
몸매도 아닌데 뭐
Who do I have in my life
to watch my figure for?
'브리짓 존스의 일기' 또 봤냐?
Oh, God, did you watch
Bridget Jones again?
아니, 너네는 다 커플이잖아
No, it's just that
everybody's got someone.
쉘든은 에이미가 있고,
하워드는 약혼했어
Sheldon's with Amy,
Howard's getting married,
넌 내 동생이랑 사귀고
you're dating my sister.
하워드도 이제 곧 결혼하니
Now that Howard's
getting married,
옛 여친을 부풀려서
너한테 선물하겠지
maybe he'll inflate one of
his old girlfriends for you.
이게 다 누구 책임인지 알아?
You know who I blame
for my loneliness?
미국 때문이지
The United States of America.
너네 영화랑 텔레비전에는
Your movies and your TV shows
promised streets paved
빵빵한 몸매의 금발녀만 나와
with beautiful blonde women
with big bazongas.
파이 하나 더 먹으면
너도 빵빵해질 거야
Eat another pie,
you'll have your own bazongas.
잔인해
That's cruel.
난 허리부터 살이 붙는다고
You know it goes
straight to my hips.
여러분, 집중합시다
Gentlemen, please focus.
불을 뿜는 드래곤이 등장했어
You're facing
a fire-breathing dragon.
이제 그만하고 싶다
I don't know if I want
to play anymore.
여자친구가 없어서?
Because you don't have
a girlfriend?
단지 그런 이유라면
Well, good Lord,
if that becomes a reason not
'던전 앤 드래곤'은
곧 망할 거야
to play Dungeons & Dragons, this
game's in serious trouble.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
DC 기타 미국드라마 갤러리
The Big Bang Theory 5x03
The Pulled Groin Extrapolation
Original Air Date on September 29, 2011
자막 공대언니
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
비키니라인 제모에도
이 왁스를 쓰자
Now, I assume we use
this same wax later on
to neaten up
each other's bikini regions.
내 비키니라인은 정리됐어
Yeah, my bikini region
is fine.
놀랍지도 않지
Who's shocked? I'm not.
(giggles)
베르나데트,
결혼 준비는 어떻게 되가?
So, Bernadette, how's the
wedding planning going?
들러리가 되고 싶어서
묻는 건 아냐
And I'm not asking
as a prospective bridesmaid.
날 뽑아줘
Pick me! Pick me!
어제는 케이크 시식하러 갔어
We went cake-tasting yesterday.
라지도 따라왔는데
Raj came along.
울면서 샘플을 반이나 먹더라
He cried and ate half
the samples.
저런, 많이 외로운가 보다
Oh, the poor guy's so lonely.
누구 소개해주면 어떨까?
We should set him up
with someone.
연구실에 괜찮은 여자 있는데
You know, I met
a really cute girl at work.
임상시험 대상자랑 결혼했어
She's married to a guy
in one of our drug trials.
저기
Well, hello?
이미 결혼했잖아
She's married.
남편이 심부전 환자인데
Yeah, but her husband is in
serious congestive
heart failure,
플라시보 그룹에 배정 받았대
*플라시보 : 가짜 약
and a little birdie told me
he's in the placebo group.
그럼 1순위는
곧 과부가 될 여자로 하자
Okay, so future
grief-stricken widow
is the one to beat.
주문할까?
Are we ready to order?
잠깐
One moment.
실험 중이야
I'm conducting
an experiment.
'던전 앤 드래곤' 주사위로?
With Dungeons
& Dragons dice?
응, 이제부터 사소한 결정은
주사위로 결정할 거야
Yes. From here on in,
I've decided
to make all trivial decisions
with a throw of the dice,
뇌를 자유롭게 하고 싶어
thus freeing up my mind
남에게 깨우침을 주는
내 본무에 집중할래
do what it does best--
enlighten and amaze.
14 페이지에 7번
Page 14,
item seven.
어떤 메뉴야?
So, what's for dinner?
옥수수 사이드디쉬야
A side of corn
succotash.
재밌군
Hmm. Interesting.
하워드, 잠깐 볼까?
Um, Howard, can I see you
for a minute, please?
친구들한테 자랑하려고?
I don't want to show any more
of your friends
이젠 어린이용 의자에
앉기 싫어
how I can fit
in the booster seats.
그런 거 아니니까 따라와
Uh, no, that's not it.
Just come with me, please.
옥수수랑 뭘 마실지 볼까
Let's see what I'll be washing
that succotash down with.
마가리타 피쳐
A pitcher of margaritas.
정말 마시고 싶어?
Do you really want that?
그게 좋은 점이야
That's the great thing.
내 의지는 상관 없어
It doesn't matter.
더 중요한 문제를
생각 중이거든
My mind is freed up to think
about more important things.
지금은 무슨 생각하는데?
What's it thinking
about now?
햄버거랑 레몬에이드
Hamburgers and lemonade.
라지,
소개해주고 싶은 친구가 있어
Um, Raj, there's someone
I want you to meet.
스핀바이크 강좌에서
만난 에밀리야
This is my friend Emily.
I know her from my spin class.
에밀리는 청각장애가 있어
Raj, relax.
She can't hear you. She's deaf.
에밀리, 내 친구 라지야
Emily, this is
our friend Raj.
Oh!
너네 정말 잘 어울린다
Look at you guys
just hitting it off.
난 너무 착해
I am so good.
Hi.
만나서 반갑대
She says, "It's
nice to meet you""
진심이야?
Does she really mean that
아님 비꼬는 식의 손짓이야?
or was she signing it
sarcastically?
라지도 만나서 반갑대요
Raj says it's nice
to meet you, too.
가족이 기다리고 있어서
가봐야 한대
She says she has to go
back to her family,
페니한테 번호를 받아서
but Penny has her
number if you want
문자로 더 얘기하재
to text her and
get together.
그래, 난 쿨하게 나갈래
Okay, I'm going to play it cool.
좋을 대로 하라고 해줘
Tell her,
"Maybe. Whatever, babe."
문자 줄 거에요
He'll text you.
데이트가 생겼어
Look at that. I have a date.
난 다시 미국을 사랑해
I love America again.
이제 디저트를 골라볼까
And now for dessert...
제발, 초코 선데이 아이스크림
Come on, hot fudge sundae,
come on, hot fudge sundae.
바로 그거야
Bam!
That's what I'm talking about!
에밀리가 도착하자 마자
Okay, as soon
as she gets here,
내가 개의치 않다는 걸
보여주기 위해
so she knows
I'm cool with it,
청각장애에 대한
농담을 할게
I'm going to make a joke
about her being deaf.
혹시 그거 들었어?
I was thinking, "Hey,
did you hear the one about...?
참, 넌 못 듣지
Oh, no, I bet you didn't."
뚱뚱한 솔로로 살고 싶은 거냐
Maybe we should revisit
your lonely fat guy plan.
도착했다
Oh, she's here.
농담은 빼
No joke.
늦어서 미안하대
She says she's sorry
she's late.
괜찮다고 해줘
Tell her
it doesn't matter.
천상의 궁전에 있는
호수 속 오팔 빛깔의 백합처럼
Tell her, her eyes shimmer
like opalescent lilies
눈이 아름답게 반짝이시네요
in the lake of the palace
of the celestial maidens.
정말?
Really?
첫 대사가 그 따위야?
That's the first thing
you want to say?
밤새도록 생각한 거야
I worked on it all night.
Use it.
오팔 빛깔은
수화로 모르겠어
Look, I don't know the
sign for opalescent.
그럼 철자로 풀어
Then spell it.
철자도 모른다고
I don't know how to spell it.
분위기 깨지 마
You're blowing this for me!
눈이 참 아름다워요
He likes your eyes.
원시인이나 할법한 말이잖아
You're making me sound
like a caveman.
너도 눈이 예쁘대
She says, "Thank you.
You have nice eyes, too."
아이는 몇 몇이나
갖고 싶은지 물어보고
Really? Ask her how many
children she wants,
대답에 상관없이
나도 같은 마음이라고 해줘
and whatever number she says,
say, "Me, too."
안돼
No.
제임스 얼 존스처럼
섹시한 목소리라고 전해줘
Fine. Tell her I have a deep,
sexy voice
like James Earl Jones.
제임스 얼 존스 목소리가
어떤지 모르시잖아
She doesn't know what James
Earl Jones sounds like.
그럼 거짓말인 줄 모르겠네
Great.
Then she won't know I'm lying.
또 뭘 알려줘야
나한테 반할까?
Let's see, what else
can I tell you about me
that would make you
like me?
전 음악을 좋아해요
Ooh, I love music.
음악 좋아하시나요?
Do you love music?
정말 그렇게 물어봐?
You really want
to ask her that?
하긴, 음악은 누구나 좋아하지
You're right.
Everyone loves music.
악기 하냐고 물어보네
She says, "Do you play
an instrument?"
아뇨
No,
하지만 6살 때
밴드를 시작하려 했어요
but when I was
six years old,
I tried to start
a boy band called
'프랭키 볼리우드 가다'
Frankie Goes
to Bollywood.
다른 애들이 가입하지 않아서
But I couldn't get
any other boys to join,
부모님께서 하인을 시켰죠
so my parents asked
the servants
백댄서 해주라고요
to be my backup dancers.
잠깐, '하인'을 손짓할 때
Wait, when you sign
"servants,"
자랑하지는 말고
겸손하게 전달해줘
don't sign it
like I'm bragging.
Sign it in a way
that I sound humble
조금은 부각되도 좋아
with just a hint of
"That's right, I had servants."
뭐라고 지껄이는 거야?
Do you hear yourself
지껄여도 못 듣잖아,
이 통역 원숭이야
Yes, but she doesn't.
So get signing, hand monkey.
매일 산타 할아버지께
편지를 썼어요
I think I wrote a letter
to Santa Claus every day.
크리스마스 날 아침이 되니
And then on Christmas morning,
트리 밑에 리본을 맨
강아지가 있더라고요
under the tree is
a little puppy
with a red ribbon.
(chuckles)
뭐해?
What are you doing?
베르나데트한테
늦는다고 문자 중이야
Texting Bernadette that
I'm gonna be late.
무슨 얘기 하는 거야?
Dude, what is she saying?
그냥 강아지 에피소드야
It's a funny story
about a puppy.
웃어주면 돼
Just smile and laugh.
(chuckles)
- 그만 웃어
- 왜?
- Quick, quick, stop smiling.
- What? Why?
강아지가 질식해서 죽었대
The puppy died-- it
choked on a doll head.
슬픈 표정!
Sad face, sad face!
불빛 때문에
잘 안 보일 거에요
It's a little hard
to see with the city lights,
여기 W모양은
카시오페이아 자리이고
but that W-shaped constellation
is Cassiopeia.
저쪽에 보이는
안드로메다의 어머니에요
And she was the mother
of Andromeda who's over there.
별들이 반짝여요
Look, pretty stars.
다 왔어
This is her car.
다음에 또 보면 좋겠대
She hopes she can see you again
sometime.
좋아
Good, good.
Oh, boy,
좀 도와줘
help me out here.
혹시 키스 받기 원하고 있어?
Does she want me
to kiss her or not?
난 수화를 하지,
마음은 못 읽어
I speak sign language,
I don't read minds.
너라면 키스하겠어?
If you were me,
would you kiss her?
응, 난 스킨십 왕이니까
Yeah, but I'm a make out king.
나 너무 멋졌어
I was so smooth
on that date.
내가 멋있게 만들어 줬잖아
You? I made
you smooth.
이 멍청아
You were an idiot.
어쨌든,
키스는 내가 받았어
Whatever, dude.
She kissed me.
네 입술에 했지만
It might've been
on your lips,
내가 받아야 할 키스였지
but it was my kiss.
그럼 둘 다 키스했다고 치자
Oh, fine. Let's agree
she kissed both of us.
그래
Okay.
수염이 멋져, 쉘든
Mustache is looking good
there, Sheldon.
다 주사위 덕분이지
Don't thank me.
Thank the dice.
얼굴의 몇 퍼센트를
면도해야 할지 정해줬어
They told me what percentage
of my face to shave.
아직도 그 짓이냐?
Why are you still doing this?
효과가 좋잖아
Because it's working.
지난 몇 주 동안
In the past few weeks,
사소한 결정을
할 필요가 없어서
unburdened by
trivial decisions,
권위 있는 학술지에
공동저자로 논문 2편을 올렸어
I've co-authored
two papers
in notable peer-reviewed
journals,
히그스 입자를 얻어내기
어려운 이유도 거의 알아냈어
and I'm close to
figuring out why
the Large Hadron
Collider has yet
to isolate the Higgs
boson particle.
속옷을 안 입어서
고환이 쓸리기도 했잖아
You left out,
got chafed testicles
because you no longer
wear underpants.
얻는 것이 있으면
잃는 것도 있는 법이다
The dice giveth
and the dice taketh away.
라지 또 에밀리랑 있나?
Is Raj out
with Emily again?
응, 매일 저녁 만나더라
Yeah, every night
for the last month.
여자친구가 생겼다니
믿기지 않아
Wow, can't believe
he has a girlfriend.
나도
Me neither.
라지와 에밀리에 대한
재밌는 소식이 있어
Here's some other fun news
on the Raj/Emily front.
다이아몬드 귀걸이를 선물하고
차도 임대해줬대
He gave her a pair of diamond
earrings and leased her a car.
정말?
You're kidding.
라지가 이용 당한다고 생각해?
You think she's taking
advantage of him?
그럴 리가
Oh, of course not.
에밀리는 그런 짓 못해
She wouldn't do
something like that.
귀가 들리지 않잖아
She's deaf.
그래도 꽃뱀일 수 있지
Deaf women can't be
gold diggers?
장애인은 착해, 레너드
Handicapped people
are nice, Leonard.
모두가 아는 사실이야
Everyone knows that.
너네한테 도움이 될만한
정보를 갖고 있어
Yeah, I actually
have information about Raj
that would be helpful
with this discussion.
얘기해줄래?
Could you tell us?
어디 보자
Let's see.
뱀 눈이 걸렸어, 미안
Snake eyes. Sorry, bud.
잠깐
Wait, hang on.
더블이잖아,
다시 굴려
Doubles.
Roll again.
자, 들어봐
Okay, get this.
선물을 갖다 바쳐도
신경 쓸 문제는 아냐
It doesn't matter if
he's showering her with gifts,
쿠트라팔리네는
엄청난 부자야
because the Koothrappalis
are vastly wealthy.
엄청난 부자라니?
What do you mean
"vastly wealthy"?
부자는 돈이 많다는 의미고
Well, "wealthy" means
a lot of money.
엄청나다는 건
큰 규모를 뜻해
"Vastly" means even more.
뭘 이해 못 하는 건지 모르겠네
I'm not sure
what's tripping you up.
부자는 맞는데 그 정도는 아니잖아
Look, I know they have money.
I don't think it's that much.
네가 잘못 알고 있어
No, you're wrong.
알다시피 몇 년 전에
난 공증인이 되었지
As you know, a few years ago,
I achieved one of
my lesser dreams
and became a notary public.
걔네 은행 서류 공증을
나한테 받았었는데
Well, from
time to time,
I notarize
banking documents for Raj.
그냥 부자가 아니라
재벌 수준이야
The Koothrappalis aren't just
rich, they're Richie Rich rich.
그게 얼만데?
Well, so how much is that?
브루스 웨인이랑
스크루지 맥덕 사이야
About halfway between
Bruce Wayne and Scrooge McDuck.
말도 안돼
What the hell?
지난 번 동물원에 갔을 때
The last time
we went to the zoo,
그 자식한테 츄러스 사줬다고
that son of a bitch
made me buy him a churro.
얘들아, 난 통화하고 올게
Listen, guys, I'm sorry,
I don't mean to be rude,
내가 사랑하는 라지 동생이랑
but I need to go call Raj's
sister, who I love so much.
엄청나게 사랑하지
So vastly much.
그 정도 부자면
아직 별 거 아니네
Okay, so he's got money,
and it's a few gifts and a car.
카드값도 다 내줬어
And she got him to pay off
all her credit cards.
카드값까지?
What? He paid off
her credit cards?
젠장, 라지랑 몇 달만 사귈걸
Damn it, I could've dated Raj
for a couple months.
하지만 그러지 않았겠지,
난 그런 여자 아냐
But I-I wouldn't have, because
I'm not that kind of girl.
라지랑 얘기 좀 해야겠어
We should really talk to Raj.
사랑에 빠진 놈이
말을 들을 리가 없지
He's not going to listen,
he's in love.
어떻게 해야 할지 모르겠지?
Can't figure out what to do?
나도 그랬던 시절이 있어
I remember those days.
자, 그럼 난...
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have to...
계속 여기 있을게
stay right here.
좋은 생각 아닌 거 같아
Yeah, this is a bad idea.
- 그냥 가자
- 안돼
- We should go.
- No.
내가 주선했잖아
I'm the one that
introduced him to her.
말은 해봐야지
I've got to
say something.
Wow.
내 친구랑 약혼한 사이잖아
You're engaged
to my friend.
베르나데트는 내가 어디서
시동을 걸든 상관 안해
Hey, Bernadette doesn't mind
where I get my motor running,
주차만 제대로 하면 된다고
as long as I park
in the right garage.
너 같은 놈이 약혼자라니
I can't believe
you're engaged to my friend.
온다
(whispers):
Oh, here she comes.
그래, 그렇게 속삭여야
귀머거리가 못 듣지
Smart. Whisper so the deaf chick
can't hear you.
Hi.
Oh, hey, hi.
반가워요
Nice to see you.
라지에 대해 얘기 좀 할까?
Um, can we talk
to you about Raj?
응, 무슨 일이야?
She says, "Sure,
what about him""
어디서부터 하지
Okay, um, gosh,
how do I start?
라지는 순진한 남자야
Um, see, Raj is
kind of naive.
연애 경험도 별로 없어
I mean, he hasn't dated
a whole lot of women.
그래서 좀 걱정이 되는데
And I'm concerned that,
without meaning to,
라지를 이용하는 게
아니면 좋겠어
you might be
taking advantage of him.
지금까지 선물도
많이 받았잖아
You know, by letting him buy you
a bunch of expensive things.
그리고
And I-I...
하워드, 집중!
Howard, focus.
통역 좀 해줘
Tell her what I'm saying.
알았어
Right.
꽃뱀 맞나요?
Are you a gold digger or not?
어쩌고 저쩌고
Oh, uh, something,
something,
이 뭐 같은 여자야
who the something do
you think you are?
내 일에 신경 끄고
Mind your own
something business
뭐나 처먹어라
and go something
yourself.
(chuckles):
Oh.
아, 이해했다
Wait, I got
this now.
나 화났어
I'm so mad at you!
잠깐만
Okay, wait...
헬스장에서
여자친구를 기습하다니
How dare you ambush my
girlfriend at the gym!
기습까지는 아니였어
We didn't mean
for it to be an ambush.
소리를 못 들으니까
몰래 다가가는 줄 알았겠지
Just, it's kind of impossible
not to sneak up on deaf people.
이제보니 말 잘하네
And hey, since when
are you so chatty?
취했어
I'm hammered.
라지, 들어와
Raj, come here.
이 여자는 멀리하는게 좋아
This girl is trouble.
선물 주고 섹스로 보답 받으면
그게 대체 무슨 관계니?
I mean, what kind of
relationship is it
where you buy her gifts
and she gives you sex?
나한테는 최고의 관계야
The best one I ever had!
Okay, come on.
더 좋은 사람
만날 수 있잖아
You know you
can do better.
Aha.
무슨 소린지 알겠다
I see what's going on here.
우리의 뜨거운 밤 이후
You and I had
our crazy night together,
다른 여자랑 있는 꼴을
못 보겠구나
and now you can't stand
to see me with another woman.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
- It's okay.
그런 감정은
너도 어쩔 수 없겠지
I can't get mad
at your feelings.
아무런 감정 없어
I don't have feelings.
그래, 좋아
Yeah, that's good.
계속 그렇게 생각해
Keep telling
yourself that.
부자라는 걸 아니
좀 귀여워졌네
He is cuter
now that I know he's rich.
뭔가 준비했어
I have a surprise
for you.
눈을 가려봐
Cover your eyes.
이제 봐도 돼
Open them.
진짜 루비야
It's a real ruby.
조금 비싸긴 한데
It was a little
expensive,
사랑의 가치는 매길 수 없어
but no one can put
a price on love.
까르띠에에서 그럴듯한
가격을 부르긴 했지
Although, the people at Cartier
took a pretty good shot at it.
(Skype ringtone playing)
엄마, 아빠
Oh, Mummy, Daddy.
기분 좋은 서프라이즈네
What a nice surprise.
덕분에 기분 잡쳤다
No, it's not a nice surprise,
it's a bad surprise.
페니가 그러더라
Penny called us.
페니?
Penny?
새 여자친구한테
재산을 갖다 바친다며?
She told us
you're spending all our money
on your new girlfriend.
선물 몇 개만 해줬어
I just got her a
couple of things.
나도 받는다고
She gives me things, too.
난 산부인과 의사야
Yeah, yeah, I'm
a gynecologist.
뭘 받는지 짐작이 간다
I know exactly
what she gives you.
좋은 가정에서 자란
착한 인도 여자를 만나야지
You need to find a nice
Indian girl from a good family.
계속 만나기만 해,
넌 국물도 없어
If you keep seeing this woman,
you're cut off.
사랑하는 여자를 저울질하라고?
What? You're going to make me
choose between the woman I love
내가 그만큼 아끼는 돈이랑?
and the money I... have
very strong feelings for?
맘대로 해
It's up to you.
난 사랑을 택하겠어
Well, I choose love.
이런 어리석은 놈
(scoffs)
You're an idiot.
사랑은 오래가지 않아
Love doesn't last.
언젠가는 알게 될텐데 뭘
Well, he's going to
find out eventually.
더 생각해봐
Think about it.
계속 사귀면
용돈 없을 거래
My parents are making me
choose between money and you.
난 네가 더 중요해
I choose you.
차는 아마 돌려줘야 할 거야
No, I think we'll have
to return the car.
응, 목걸이도
And that necklace,
yeah, that, too.
그런 건 중요하지 않아
But none of those
things matter,
우리도 소중한 재산이 있어
because we have
something better.
사랑이 있잖아
We have love.
페니, 너무 마음이 아파
Oh, Penny, I
hurt so bad.
그래, 그래
I know, I know.
곁에 있는 상상을 하면서
TV 음소거 버튼을 누르기도 해
Sometimes I put
the TV on mute
just to pretend
she's still with me.
그런데 눈물이 나서
자막을 못 읽겠어
But I can't watch the closed
captioning without crying.
불쌍해라
Oh, I'm so sorry.
기분 풀어주고 싶다
I wish I could
make you feel better.
정말?
Seriously?
이렇게 상처 받았는데
작업 걸고 있어?
I'm heartbroken and
you're hitting on me?
뭐?
아냐!
What?! No!
페니,
넌 괜찮은 여자야
Look, Penny,
you're great,
부모님이랑 상의해봤는데
but I had a long talk
with my parents,
인도 여자를 만나면
마세라티를 주신대
and they said if I date an
Indian girl, I get a Maserati.
Mmm.
오, 치즈케익
Oh, cheesecake,
여자만큼 좋아
you're just as good as a woman,
같이 섹스는 못 하지만
even though I can't
have sex with you.
전자렌지에 몇 초 돌려봐
Try throwing it in the microwave
for a few seconds.
화장실 갈까 아니면
집에 갈 때까지 참을까?
Should I use the rest room
or wait until we get home?
방광 좀 비우게 해주라
Come on, papa needs
to void his bladder.
버터밀크 3잔 후
이런 결과라니
Oh, that's not what you want
to see after three buttermilks.
계산서야
Here you go, boys.
준비 되면 불러
I'll pick it up
when you're ready.
잘 먹었어, 친구야
Thanks for dinner,
buddy.
그래, 넌 통이 커서 좋아
Yeah, real big of you.
빨리, 빨리
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
팁도 후하게 부탁해
Oh, and don't cheap
out on the tip.
돈 많은 거 다 아니까
We all know
you're loaded now.
공대언니 블로그
http://tbbt.tistory.com
== sync, corrected by elderman ==